How to get the ends note of their link, at least consider an example if we have this linked list,
the first element is 18, second is 66 and the third is one one nine.
OK.
We have three elements inside this link and not.
Think of this.
We are going to search for the second or two that get that and not which is do.
So we are searching and we need to get the second nod inside this link.
At least for that, I need to search for the first one.
If it is there and the swan and search for the second, which is at second, at the second and decks,
and we get it by making this happen, by creating a damp variable.
So what does this means?
I will create get an A..
It is a method that takes in the perimeter a structure structure no reference had referencing to the
head and end index.
OK.
So what we are searching for, we are searching for their fourth due to the right.
I have called this method get and note, and I passed the hat and do this number two.
We are telling that we need the second, the second index.
We we need the not at index number two.
No.
We created structure, not them equal to had we start by temp equal to their difference to the head.
So what is the head of the of this linkage list?
It's the first position and we reference this stamp to it.
We create and count equal to zero.
And we create a while loop.
So while loop if count equal equal to end x, then return stamp and with the date, OK, the return
that -- of that data.
So and count increased by one stamp equal to them the next.
So reference that temp stamp move the cursor of the temp by using temp equals temp there to financing
for that next.
OK.
Otherwise, if you don't, if we have like five elements inside the linked list and I need that 10th
index, the 10th index is not included because that linkage list contains only five elements.
OK.
It's maximum index is four.
The numbers start from zero one two three four five elements.
OK, so it will return minus one.
Otherwise, if we get the index and everything is correct, then returned the data of at the index equal
to two or the past index.
OK.
This is how we get the arms not of the link, at least by moving the temporary cursor or the temporary
pointer through the nodes and searching for the specific and.